Oh, Vincent!
I love you!
No, we mustn't, Miss Sonia!
My betrothed is still waiting
for me in the West...
Berlint in Love
But your parents decided
on her, didn't they?
I'll make you forget her!
No, we mustn't, Miss Sonia!
I can't breathe...
Oh, Anya!
I'm nearby because I was shopping.
Can I come over right now?
What? I can? Thank you! I'll be right there!
Good day, Anya!
Are you alone?! You're not alone, are you?!
Becky, are you actually
Shwoop-man, who could teleport?
Today's the day I finally
meet my precious Loid
and propose that we begin courtship!
You mustn't commit adultery, my lady.
Papa, Becky's here.
Hey there. Welcome.
My precious Loid in the flesh!
Come, now. Introduce yourself, my lady.
Um, um... H-H-Hello.
Thank you for having me over.
I'm sorry we came over
unannounced, Mr. Forger.
Oh, it's no problem at all.
I'm sure my daughter is happy
to have a friend over.
Hello, Miss Becky.
Miss Becky... Miss Becky...
Thank you for always being such
good friends with my daughter.
Asherishk, tic-tac-toe, triangle,
smiley old guy, steam, heart?
Some kind of code?!
Come, now, my lady.
It's quite rude to roll around on
the floor at someone else's house.
Love...
Anya's seen someone like this before.
Wuv
Now, behave yourself, my lady.
I will come pick you up
when it's time to go home.
Please look after my lady.
Of course.
The way her attendant carries herself...
She's clearly a former soldier
who's seen countless battlefields.
I guess that's to be expected
of the Blackbells.
Wanna explore Anya's home?
Well, I guess this is my first
time actually coming inside.
This is the living room!
What? This isn't just the storage
space by your front door?
This is Anya's room!
Oh, this is even more compact
than my little Wiesel's doghouse.
Isn't it hard to breathe in here?
Let's stop exploring.
Oh, really?
By the way, where's the wife?
Mama is out walking Bond.
This is my chance!
Oh, my precious Loid!
We mustn't, Miss Becky! I have a wife.
But your parents decided on
this marriage, didn't they?
Completely
Unfounded
But...
I'll use my charms to make
you forget about her!
Oh, Miss Becky!
Becky's gonna become Anya's mama?!
I'm sure Anya would be happy
if I were her mama, too.
Let's move somewhere much bigger.
A castle!
Come, Anya. Let's head to
school together. By helicopter.
Mama!
Our meals will be prepared
by world-class chefs daily.
Delicious!
Yum.
Our attendants will help with
all the annoying stuff.
Let's go out and play.
Yay!
She brings up good points!
I'm sorry, Mama.
I'm gonna side with Becky for just a
bit for the sake of world-class chefs.
Papa! You should play with us, too!
Nice assist, Anya!
Er, play?
W-W-W-We can just chat.
U-Um... Um... M-My...
Mwy name is Becky Blackbell!
Hm? Yes, I know that.
World-class chefs! World-class chefs!
The Blackbells are quite famous,
so of course I knew about you even before
you and Anya ended up in the same class.
As an important source of information.
He's known about me?
I have various routes to obtain my intel,
but there might be some useful information
I can gain from the Blackbells'
daughter, as well.
I guess I'll chat with her.
Papa immediately goes into work mode.
Is your father well?
I heard he's been busy with the
restructuring going on in the industry.
Um, yes... But my papa is nice,
so whenever he has a day off,
he always plays with me.
Last time, we went to the movies!
Next time, I'd love to go with you.
Oh, really? What did you go see?
Did you go to the theater by the river?
There are a lot of great
restaurants around there.
The time her father is off from work,
the range of his activities,
his habits, what he likes to eat...
Plenty of potentially useful information.
Oh, um... We saw a romance...
H-He's trying to find out my preferences?!
He even mentioned restaurants...
Wait, did he just ask me out?!
Did he ask me out just now?!
You two must be really close.
Do you go out with your family often?
Do you and your parents have
fun together at home, too?
Currently, there's nothing suggesting
that Blackbell Heavy Industries
is involved any plans for war,
but it wouldn't hurt to obtain some
information for the future just in case.
P-P-P-Papa loves to play chess.
I don't understand it at all,
but he always makes me play.
Uh, and...
He's asking so much about my family!
Could it be that my precious
Loid is preparing for the future
and planning a serious courtship with me?!
He's looking at me oh so intently!
She's wild.
I've returned.
Borf!
Oh? Welcome, Miss Becky!
Here comes the final boss!
World-class chefs! World-class chefs!
World-class chefs!
Right when my precious Loid
was actively pursuing me...
H-Hello, Mrs. Forger.
Oh, you're so adorable.
Behold, Becky! This is our Bond!
Borf!
My precious Loid's heart is
starting to lean more toward me!
Behold, Becky!
Just one more push, Becky!
You need to give it all you've
got right here and now!
Use what you've learned from your dramas!
Oh, Loid.
I bought the ingredients for dinner.
Thanks, Yor.
She's showing off how domestic she is?
Hmph, how naïve.
That's not enough to win
my precious Loid's heart!
Papa and Mama are already married, though.
As Jonathan from Berlint in Love said,
even when men get married,
they want their partners to be real women.
Huh? That wasn't much of a reaction.
Maybe I didn't bat my eyelashes enough.
But Tommy said it's really sexy
when a girl lets down her hair
or puts it back up.
I know Miss Becky has been really
looking forward to meeting you, Loid,
so she must be very happy.
Perhaps this is how she expresses that.
Ah... right...
I've made us some tea.
Why don't you have a seat over there, Loid?
My precious Loid is right next
to me! He's right next to me!
Showing mercy by having him sit next
to me? The missus must be going crazy.
I know. She must've admitted defeat
after seeing my hair attack!
This is your chance, Becky!
Go all in!
She doesn't seem to be feeling well.
Um, my precious Loid, about what
you were saying earlier...
Are you interested in my family?
"My precious"?
Oh, sorry. I didn't mean anything by it.
I may have asked too much.
I figured she wouldn't notice since she's
a child, but I may have gone too far.
What?! You mean you were just
playing games with my heart?!
What are you talking about?
Yor's going to get the wrong idea somehow.
Oh, Loid! He must have been playing
with Miss Becky before I got home.
He's so kind.
Look at her smiling like
she's won this round.
She's so sure she's won!
Do I really not have a chance with him?
Are my chefs going to lose?
Fine, I'm going for broke!
I'll use the final attack that
Penelope used on Tommy!
Oh, dear. I think I'm getting a little drunk.
Uh, it's tea.
According to Berlint in Love,
this is a taboo move that 100%
makes the guy fall for you!
There's no turning back now!
This is war, missus!
Er, Yor, this isn't...
Oh, no!
I've somehow managed to put
alcohol in a child's drink!
Whatever shall I do?!
No, really. It's just tea.
Did I steep the tea leaves for too long?!
The hospital! Yes!
Let's go to the hospital!
Hey, wait!
Yor?!
Are you all right, Miss Becky?!
Do you feel nauseous?!
I'm fine! I'm fine, really! Just put me down!
You mustn't underestimate
acute alcohol poisoning!
No, really! It's not!
But I'm not sure exactly what kind
of doctor should see you!
You should probably go
to the emergency room!
We're almost there! Hang in there!
You'll die if you fall asleep!
I'm pretty sure I won't!
"Hee-hee-hoo!" Like that! "Hee-hee-hoo!"
That's not it, either!
Please wait, ma'am...
That's not it... I...
I was just lying because I wanted
to date my precious Loid!
I'm not drunk!
What?!
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
I'm so happy you're all right.
Huh?
Can you stand?
Y-You're not going to yell at me?
Why would I? You're safe and sound.
No, I mean about my precious Loid.
It makes me happy to hear
that Loid is so loved.
I mean, he is quite lovely.
Sh... She has such a huge heart!
She's okay with infidelity?!
I'm the one who should be sorry.
I took you this far because I panicked.
No, that's my fault.
I'm such a failure compared to Loid.
B-But my precious Loid chose you!
How did you shoot an arrow
through his heart?!
I want to know!
Shoot him... huh?
But I haven't shot Loid!
And I don't use a bow and arrows.
Huh?
Hm?
Uh...
Oh, um, the reason Loid chose me is, um...
I can't tell her that our priorities aligned.
My memories are a bit fuzzy,
but I believe he's told me before...
It's because I'm strong.
Because you're strong?!
M-My precious Loid prefers strong women?!
I mean, his wife is definitely really strong.
Well, more like she's built very tough!
Hey! There they are.
Becky!
Becky, you forgot your bag.
My precious Loid was so worried
that he came looking for me?!
Your bag.
Strong... I need to somehow
show him that I'm strong!
There must be something...
That's it!
Oh, I suddenly feel like
I want to throw down a hammer!
What the heck kind of feeling is that?
I really don't understand
the children of rich people.
Mister, I'd like to play this.
Wha? You gonna be able to pay, kid?
Chefs! Chefs! Chefs! Chefs! Chefs! Chefs!
Here I go!
Che—
You give up?
I'm a weak woman.
I'm such a weak and awful woman...
A-Are you all right?!
My precious Loid will never
notice me if I'm like this.
Super Earpick
Ultra Nail Clippers
Hyper Toothbrush
Aha. Miss Becky must've wanted to give
the top prize to Loid as a gift.
I'm going to borrow this for a second.
Hup.
First place! First place! First place!
I-I did it...
I couldn't control my strength again.
So this is strength...
My precious Loid is staring
so intently at his wife!
So that is it! He really
does prefer strong women!
Yor...
You've got the wrong idea, Loid!
I used to be the apprentice of
a professional hammer user!
Just look at his beautiful, round eyes!
He's definitely in love with her!
I guess I'm no match for you, missus.
Huh?
Your heart is as vast as the sky,
and you're stronger than the earth itself.
You're the perfect lady.
I want to become your apprentice!
I want to become strong like you!
L-Like me?
All right. Then let's train together!
Yes, ma'am!
And then, one day,
I'll make my precious Loid...
I've come to get you, my lady.
Hah!
No, Miss Becky. You need to
twist your hips more! Hah!
Hah!
Ah, déjà vu...
Yeah, Mama's way more fun to be around.
Hah!
Berlint General Hospital,
Thursday
You're on vacation starting
tomorrow, aren't you, Dr. Forger?
Nightfall's Daily Life
Yes, I'm sorry.
Nah, you always work
too much, so it's perfect.
Have a great time and relax.
I'm so jealous, sir. Tell me
all about it next time.
Sure. Thank you very much.
I'm sorry for giving you extra work while
I'm gone, but I appreciate all of you.
WISE Safe House G
That's the basic rundown of this mission.
Do you have any questions?
No, I'll be fine.
I'm counting on you, Nightfall.
Oh, and...
Take a look at this, too.
I was planning to give that mission to
Twilight once he got back from vacation,
but things have changed.
Sorry, but this is urgent.
Will you be able to do
some additional tasks?
Of course, I'll be splitting the
tasks with other agents, as well.
No, I'll do all of this myself.
I appreciate your dedication,
but you have your own mission, as well.
I don't intend to destroy
all of you with overwork.
But I don't believe anyone other
than me can fulfill these tasks.
Fine. But don't push yourself too hard.
Agent Twilight is WISE's number one spy.
None of the missions that a spy of
his caliber is tasked with are easy.
But for me, this is a huge opportunity.
Twilight has taught me so very much...
The techniques of a spy,
how to present myself...
I use all those skills to the
fullest to complete my missions.
And whenever I perfectly
execute my missions...
I'm going to take the role of his wife.
Yes! Now I'm sure Twilight
will finally figure out
that I'm the one best
suited to be his partner!
But...
This is still not enough to
secure complete victory.
In order to defeat Yor Briar...
In order to become Mrs. Forger...
I need more!
More!
Monday:
Morning
Those are all of the documents concerning
your patients while you were gone.
Thanks.
Three days later and Twilight is
as lovely as ever. I love you.
How was your vacation? Any changes?
Like maybe finding a huge flaw
in your current wife for Strix?
There were a handful of troublesome
things like Anya being selfish
and the whole bomb threat, but...
No, not really.
I see.
Tch.
What about you?
Were there any changes while I was gone?
I worked very hard on my missions
so I can be a woman you'd admire.
Next time, I'm going to
beat that woman, too.
So you should choose me to be your wife!
No, not really.
I see.
Nightfall did?
Yes.
She was determined to take
on all the tasks herself.
She did excellent work.
To think that Nightfall would take
over for me while I was gone.
I'm sure she had her own missions, too.
Souvenirs
By the way... I had some extra souvenirs
left after handing them out to everyone else.
Do you want them?
Souvenirs
She's glaring at me so hard!
Huh? Wait, why?!
Thank you very much.
Please excuse me.
I wuv you! I wuv you! I wuv you!
I figured that was my only chance
to say anything, so I did.
I see.
Oh, Fiona.
Good morning.
I wuv him
The bright crimson that
appears right before my eyes
Stretches approximately 40,000 kilometers
Our wounds that inch closer behind us
Make us wander even more
when we're already lost
The unseeable, scentless, unmistakable future
Stabbed me in the back!
So...
Let me stay by your side tonight
Just for tonight, I'm going to be serious
Come closer to me
Even the future we prayed for
Has a different path
My dear
Our malice for each other
Might just get to us
Or maybe not
Part of the Family